SALINA HUANG

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

A friendly and enthusiastic Computer Science undergraduate with a passion for education that comes with teaching others how to code.

Highly skilled and experienced in breaking down concepts to guide students in learning new content and supportive of their learning journey.

Adept at caring for and supervising children. Good at managing sudden unexpected situations that may occur when supervising children.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021 St George Cirls High School (Graduated)

2022 - Current UNSW - Bachelor of Computer Science

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Distinction in NCSS Challenge (Newbies) 2017 (Grok Learning)
- High Distinction in Web.Comp (Intermediate) 2018 (Grok Learning)
- High Distinction in Web.Comp (Advanced) 2019 (Grok Learning)
- Perfect Score in NCSS Challenge (Intermediate) 2019 (Grok Learning)
- Distinction in ICAS SCIENCE 2018, 2017, 2016 & 2015
- Distinction in Australian Math Competition 2017

EXPERIENCE

Tutor

Pre-Uni New College (2018 - 2020)

- Supervised primary aged kids from 7-12 years old in groups of up to 15 children
- Taught classes of students Maths, Novel Study, English, and General Ability
- Guided students through difficult questions in help sessions
- Marked student Maths, English, General Ability and Novel Study workbooks

Student

UNSW High School Computing (HS1917) - 2019

- Took a programming course (1st year UNSW COMP1511 equivalent) in high school and achieved distinction
- Learnt how to program in C
- This course was where I first properly experienced and became invested in computer science, It was run by mostly volunteers and it was also where I gained interest in teaching code as they ran a volunteers program.

Participant

Girls Programming Network Workshops 2019 - 2020

- Solidified my knowledge of Python, HTML and CSS that I had already developed from previous participation in Grok programs

Student

NCSS Summer School 2020

- Participated in a 10 day camp where I learnt how to program with more advanced Python and web technology(HTTP, JSON, APIs etc.)

CONTACT INFORMATION

Salina Huang Phone: 0450503465

Email: salina.huang1@gmail.com

Campsie, 2194